{
    "subject": "resource/Jos\u00e9_Antonio_de_Mendoza,_3rd_Marquis_of_Villagarc\u00eda",
    "predicate": "ontology/monarch",
    "object": "resource/Philip_V_of_Spain",
    "human_readable": "Jos\u00e9 Antonio de Mendoza, 3rd Marquis of Villagarc\u00eda was a monarch under Philip V of Spain.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9283345937728882,
            "question": "Under which Spanish monarch did Jos\u00e9 Antonio de Mendoza serve?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8837218880653381,
            "question": "Who was Jos\u00e9 Antonio de Mendoza?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8626969456672668,
            "question": "What was the relationship between Jos\u00e9 Antonio de Mendoza and Philip V of Spain?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8006948828697205,
            "question": "Was Jos\u00e9 Antonio de Mendoza a king?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6979191303253174,
            "question": "What were the responsibilities of a monarch under Philip V of Spain?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6585591435432434,
            "question": "Were there other notable figures who served under Philip V of Spain?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6304654479026794,
            "question": "What impact did Jos\u00e9 Antonio de Mendoza have on Spanish history?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.607147753238678,
            "question": "What title did Jos\u00e9 Antonio de Mendoza hold?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5889390707015991,
            "question": "What era did Jos\u00e9 Antonio de Mendoza live in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.40484878420829773,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Philip V of Spain?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Jos\u00e9 Antonio de Mendoza, 3rd Marquis of Villagarc\u00eda was a monarch under Philip V of Spain.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4342_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What era did Jos\u00e9 Antonio de Mendoza live in?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4342_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What title did Jos\u00e9 Antonio de Mendoza hold?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4342_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What impact did Jos\u00e9 Antonio de Mendoza have on Spanish history?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4342_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4342_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4342_107.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4342_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4342_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4342_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4342_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4342_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4342_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4342_82.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4342_99.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'} \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that there is no information in the provided documents about Jos\u00e9 Antonio de Mendoza, 3rd Marquis of Villagarc\u00eda being a monarch under Philip V of Spain. The document mentioning Villagarc\u00eda (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_4342/re-ranker-msmarco/64.txt) refers to him as the president of the Audiencia of Charcas, but does not mention any monarchship or connection to Philip V of Spain."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The information provided does not support the statement that Jos\u00e9 Antonio de Mendoza, 3rd Marquis of Villagarc\u00eda was a monarch under Philip V of Spain. The documents mention his appointment as president of the Audiencia of Charcas but do not indicate any monarchic relationship with Philip V of Spain."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "Jos\u00e9 Antonio de Mendoza, 3rd Marquis of Villagarc\u00eda was not a monarch; he was a Spanish and Portuguese politician who served as the first viceroy of New Spain.",
            "category": -1
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "The provided context focuses on Antonio de Mendoza as the first viceroy of New Spain and mentions other historical figures like King Charles I of Spain, John of Austria, and the marquis of Villagarc\u00eda. There's no information connecting Jos\u00e9 Antonio de Mendoza to being a monarch under Philip V of Spain.",
            "category": -1
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The claim is wrong because Jos\u00e9 Antonio de Mendoza was not mentioned as a monarch under Philip V of Spain, instead, information about the marquis of Villagarc\u00eda being appointed as president of the Audiencia of Charcas and the context about Antonio DE MENDOZA Y PACHECO suggest that there is no connection between Jos\u00e9 Antonio de Mendoza and being a monarch.",
            "category": -1
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The context information provided does not mention Jos\u00e9 Antonio de Mendoza, 3rd Marquis of Villagarc\u00eda being a monarch. Instead, it talks about his appointment as president of the Audiencia of Charcas and his eventual decline of the post, which indicates he was an official under another authority (likely Philip II of Spain, considering the timeframe), not a monarch himself.",
            "category": -1
        }
    }
}